homelane.com 2016-11-20

# Our Commitment, Information Security - HomeLane Policies India

HomeLane.com is a website owned by Homevista Decor and Furnishing Private Limited, a company incorporated under the Indian Companies Act, 1956. Wherever the term "HomeLane" or “HomeLane Interiors” or "HomeLane.com" is used it refers to Homevista Decor and Furnishing Pvt Ltd, and its subsidiaries, controlled entities, affiliates and related parties. HomeLane provides the services through www.homelane.com ('Website' or 'Site'). At HomeLane, we are highly committed to the privacy of your data and information and in providing excellent service to all of our customers and visitors of the Website. We have prepared this Data Protection and Privacy Policy ("Policy") to inform you of the privacy principles that govern this Website. 

Unless restricted by applicable law, you agree that all your personal information collected by HomeLane through the Website may be used and disclosed as set out in this Policy. 

You are advised to read this Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by HomeLane.com you agree to the collection and use of your data by HomeLane.com and certain authorized third party service providers in the manner provided in this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use the Website. 

## What is covered in this Policy?

This Policy covers how HomeLane treats personal information that HomeLane collects and receives, including information related to your past use of the Website products and services.

When you register for our service, we would require your personal information that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and other information that is not otherwise publicly available and is essentially required for registering and receiving services from us. 

HomeLane is not responsible for any acts, deeds or things done or committed by any person not being directly employed by HomeLane. In addition, certain HomeLane.com associated/partner companies have their own privacy statements which can be viewed by clicking on their respective links. 

## Privacy – Our Commitment

At HomeLane, we are extremely committed to protect your privacy. We would like you to feel confident about us, use our services freely and recommend our services to your friends and family.

We guarantee that we will not rent and sell your personal information to third parties (except as stated in this Policy) without your consent. In the day to day operations, we will provide your information to our partners who will assist in providing our services. Your comfort, trust and confidence are of paramount importance to us. 

## What Information is collected from you.

## Profile Information

HomeLane collects the details provided by you on registration (email address, name, password, phone number, address and some profile details and interests) together with information we learn about you from your use of our service and your visits to our Site. We also collect information about the transactions you undertake including details of payments and type of cards used. We will not collect and store information related to your credit cards such as number, expiry date and CVV number.

We may collect additional information in connection with your participation in any promotions or competitions offered by us and information you provide when giving us feedback or completing profile forms. We also monitor customer traffic patterns and Site use, which enables us to improve the service we provide. We will collect only such information as is necessary and relevant to us to provide you with the services available on the Site. 

You can terminate your account at any time. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account. 

## Anonymous Information

In addition to the information that you explicitly provide during your interactions on the Site, we will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies" sent to your browser from:

  1. web server cookie stored on your hard drive
  2. an IP address, assigned to the computer which you use
  3. the domain server through which you access our service
  4. the type of computer you're using
  5. the type of web browser you're using

## Who collects the information?

We collect personal information about you as part of the registration process, which is voluntary. Other means of collecting personal information is through some contests, online events, surveys etc.

We collect anonymous information like traffic information and hardware information when you visit our Site. 

Our advertisers and partners may collect their own anonymous information through their own cookies for which we are not responsible for.

HomeLane understands the importance of protecting children's privacy, especially in an online environment. Our sites are not intentionally designed for or directed at children 18 years of age or younger. It is our policy never to knowingly collect or maintain information about anyone under the age of 18.

## Information Usage

We use your personal information to allow it to process your registration, to process any orders that you may make for any products or services displayed on the Website, provide you with improved services, contact you when it is needed by telephone, facsimile and e-mail, and to advise you of products and services which may be of interest to you, inviting you to be a participant or a respondent to an online event that is hosted on HomeLane.com. Further, the relevant information is used by HomeLane to (i) provide you with statements of your account; (ii) to communicate with you on any matter relating to the conduct of your account; and (iii) to communicate the details of any orders / processing of any orders placed by you relating to products displayed on the Website.

HomeLane may also use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the Website, our products and services and may provide such Aggregate information to third parties on an aggregate basis. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual customer. 

HomeLane may organize contests and surveys and the information collected during these events may be used by HomeLane to improve your overall customer experience. The information will only be shared with third parties on an aggregate basis. 

[For the purposes of this Policy, "Aggregate information" shall mean and include information that is recorded about users and collected into groups so that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user. Such information does not identify you individually.] 

Personal data collected by the Website may be transferred to other sites of HomeLane where it is necessary to meet the purpose for which you have submitted the information. By submitting data on this Website, you are providing explicit consent to transmission of data collected on the Website. 

We use anonymous information like traffic and other data to provide us with information to recognize the access privileges to our Site, track your participation in any of the events, providing you with better content and advertisements, help diagnose the problems with our Site and for the purposes detailed in the Policy. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosures

Profile Information  
We do not rent, sell or share your personal information to third parties -

  * Unless we have permission from you,
  * Unless we have to provide products and services that are requested by you,
  * Unless we have to help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, suspected fraud, potential threat to the safety or security of any person or organization or property or asset or rights of the Website from unauthorized use or misuse of the Website, violations of HomeLane.com terms and conditions or to defend against legal claims/proceedings
  * Unless upon occurrence of special circumstances detailed hereunder -

  1. to respond to subpoenas, court orders, judicial proceedings, or other legal processes;
  2. to enforce the terms of the Website User Terms and Conditions or the terms of this Policy;
  3. to respond to claims that any photo, text, or other material violates the rights of third parties; or
  4. to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of HomeLane, its users, or the general public.

We provide certain required personal and contact information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted business partners for the purpose of providing the required service on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

If HomeLane becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will inform you through e-mail before personal information is transferred and that may become subject to a different privacy policy. 

We may share with third parties certain pieces of Aggregate information. 

## Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. We restrict access to personal information to HomeLane employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

Although we endeavour to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. By using this Site, you agree that we will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

You further agree that you are solely responsible and liable for, and shall indemnify HomeLane against any and all costs, expenses, damages, fees, etc. that HomeLane may incur or suffer due to any personal information or other materials that you post, upload, submit, and otherwise make available on the Website, including areas of the Website that are available to the public. We have no control over and cannot protect personal information that you disclose in public areas of the Website. If you disclose your personal information in public areas, it may be collected and used by third parties, without our or your knowledge. You should also understand that by displaying your information or photographs on the Website and the internet, for the intention of showing the information / those photographs to your friends, family, acquaintances, clients, business partners, and others, that you directly intended to see the photographs, you are relinquishing certain traditional privacy rights, wherein anyone with access to the internet has the potential ability to view your information / photographs. If you do not wish to relinquish these traditional privacy rights, do not share your information / photographs. 

## Policy Compliance

HomeLane.com regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or HomeLane.com's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this Website or by e-mailing to us at hello@homelane.com. When we receive complaints at this address, it is HomeLane.com's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between HomeLane.com and an individual.

## Disputes

Any dispute, controversy or claim directly or indirectly caused by, arising out of or relating to this Policy will be governed by the laws of India and will be referred to confidential, mandatory and binding arbitration in Bangalore, India. The arbitration will be conducted on an expedited basis before a single arbitrator appointed by HomeLane in accordance with the provisions of the Indian Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996. The arbitrator's award shall be substantiated in writing and will be final and binding on you and HomeLane. Subject to the above, you agree to submit yourself to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts in Bangalore, India.

## Your Choices

By submitting your information, you consent to the use of that information as set out in this Policy. We welcome your views on this Website and the Policy. However, submitting personally identifiable information is entirely voluntary. You are not required to register with us in order to browse our Site. Please note that we offer some services only to visitors who do register.

At any point in time, you can correct and make changes to your personal information by accessing your information in My Account section of the Site. 

You may change your interests at any time and may opt-in or opt-out of any marketing / promotional / newsletters mailings. Homelane.com reserves the right to send you certain service related communication, considered to be a part of your homelane.com account without offering you the facility to opt-out. You may update your information and change your account settings at any time. 

If we plan to use your personally identifiable information for any commercial purposes, we will notify you at the time we collect that information and allow you to opt-out of having your information used for those purposes.
